<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wong&#39;s Intro Study Group</title>
    <link>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Wong&#39;s Intro Study Group</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/media/icon_huf5464b9d1790bae80d26f27b7393d023_88417_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Wong&#39;s Intro Study Group</title>
      <link>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;about page here, with more info&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mostafatouny.github.io/wong-intro-website/meetings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;meetings&#34;&gt;Meetings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;details class=&#34;spoiler &#34;  id=&#34;spoiler-0&#34;&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Plus Meeting (2) &lt;em&gt;(10/04/2022)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;details class=&#34;spoiler &#34;  id=&#34;spoiler-1&#34;&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Plus Meeting (1) &lt;em&gt;(09/04/2022)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/@mostafatouny:7/wong-intro-plus-meeting-1-09-04-2022:a&#34;&gt;Audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Objectives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure members understand the logistical way of participation and tasks&#39; solution submission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss members&#39; suggestions of problems, investigations, or projects, to be pursued by the study group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss each member&amp;rsquo;s personal goals and plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dylan Sheils&lt;/em&gt; Introduced himself. He is an undergrad student, Majored in physics and computer science, at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute university, in New York. He is interested in understanding theory of computing using physics. Had collaborative projects in universities but they didn&amp;rsquo;t go well. He had completed an introductory course on quantum computing and implemented a circuit simulator project. He&amp;rsquo;s looking more for advanced topics in quantum computing, and physics simulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; racaped the group&amp;rsquo;s previous tasks. Namely, (1) Suggesting materials and exercises for quantum computing, Through pure physics and hardware perspectives. (2) Members submission of their own interesting problems. (3) Members feedback on group&amp;rsquo;s logistics and suggestions for improvement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Joseph&lt;/em&gt; had done some quantum programming, but didn&amp;rsquo;t study quantum information or quantum error correction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; suggested coffee chats meetings, For random discussions. The goal is to booster members social relationships. &lt;em&gt;Boomer&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Dylan&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Joseph&lt;/em&gt; had agreed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; stressed members must communicate themselves, in order for the group to evolve. He illustrated the variety of activities the group might tackle altogether, including solving problems collaboratively on a live meeting, playing multiplayer games like Hanabi, and Presentation meetings where a member presents some topic in an accessible manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quotes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Joseph&lt;/em&gt;: &amp;ldquo;A reason why am I discussing this, is that I need to know where others are standing&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt;: &amp;ldquo;This is group is gradually going to evolve, but you must express yourself&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;details class=&#34;spoiler &#34;  id=&#34;spoiler-2&#34;&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Bi-weekly Meeting &lt;em&gt;(02/04/2022)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt;, The organizer faced a technical issue, and wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to participate with other eight members who joined the meeting. It was an embarrassment for him. Two &lt;em&gt;plus meetings&lt;/em&gt; are initaited, as a compensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;details class=&#34;spoiler &#34;  id=&#34;spoiler-3&#34;&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Bi-weekly Meeting &lt;em&gt;(19/03/2022)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/@mostafatouny:7/wong-intro-biweekly-19-03-2022:a&#34;&gt;Audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Objectives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Gathering.&lt;/em&gt; Members get introduced to each other, Learning about each other&amp;rsquo;s background, interests, and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Casual Discussion.&lt;/em&gt; Challenges of online study groups and how to overcome them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aaditya&lt;/em&gt; is a sophomore electric engineering student; From india. He has been doing courses in quantum computing and linear algebra; Studied deutsch-jozsa algorithm. He is interested in quantum hardware and error-correction. He had joined a study group before but it&amp;rsquo;s dead now. The problem of it was lack of interaction and discussions. He couldn&amp;rsquo;t follow-up content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Katherine&lt;/em&gt; has a bachelor in physics and math; From USA. She has no previous exposure to quantum computing, but took undergrad courses in quantum mechanics. She is interested in physical systems and molecules simulation, and wishes to get exposed to quantum computing&amp;rsquo;s applications as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rajesh&lt;/em&gt; is employed in the software industry; From india; Graduated from Mumbai university. He read &lt;a href=&#34;https://mitpress.mit.edu/books/quantum-computing-everyone&#34;&gt;quantum computing for everyone&lt;/a&gt; book. His interest is mainly in quantum programming and quantum frameworks. He struggled with math and physics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ethan&lt;/em&gt; is a CS student; interested in math and CS, algorithm design, and theoretical CS. He likes the paradigm shift of quantum computing. He is interested also in philosopy of science. He had no previous experience in study groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ethan&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; talked a little bit about philosophy, Theoretical CS, and Chi-ning&amp;rsquo;s mini-course, &lt;a href=&#34;https://cnchou.github.io/mini-course/&#34;&gt;What is Computation?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rajesh&lt;/em&gt; asked about &lt;em&gt;post-meetings&lt;/em&gt; document. &lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; explained it is for those who couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend the meeting, To answer questions &lt;em&gt;Mostafa&lt;/em&gt; asked attendees during the live meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Members are going to self-study on their own, and the next meeting, Each member is going to share his studying approach. The goal is to establish a good communication among members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;details class=&#34;spoiler &#34;  id=&#34;spoiler-4&#34;&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Intro &lt;em&gt;(15/03/2022)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://odysee.com/@mostafatouny:7/wong-intro-intro:c&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cryptpad.fr/file/#/2/file/8K7yvjk-qzUwg0T15KlyOfsr/&#34;&gt;Slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Objectives&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate group&amp;rsquo;s pedagogy, Including motivation, goals, activities, challenges, and how we&amp;rsquo;re going to get started.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
